- 确定不要去我房间? - 确定
- Are you sure you don't wanna go to my room? - No. Why?
我室友已经搬走了 就我们两个
My roommate's already moved out. We'll be all alone.
- 好吧 - 门锁好了
- All right. - The door is locked.
- 吉姆 放松 - 放松 当然
- Okay,Jim, relax. Relax. - Okay,yeah, sure.
单纯的性关系 分手前的经验
No strings attached, okay? It's just friendly good- bye sex.
当然 我知道
Yeah, right. Right, right, right, right.
只是 你知道...
But you see, it's just that...
没有开始哪来的结束
we've never even had friendly hello sex.
那你是不想做罗?
So do you not wanna do this?
想 当然想 怎么会不想
Oh, I do. Yeah. No, I definitely do.
只是...
It's just that...
这是我的第一次
you see, this is actually my first time.
不能算第一次 应该说上次
Well, not my first. It's my first time...
才是我的第一次
since my first time.
所以说 这是我的第二次
So, technically, that's my second time.
我不希望表现得太逊
And I don't... I don't wanna suck at it.
要是我的技术没有达到...
So if I'm not up to par, performance- wise...
吉姆 你实在有够扫兴
Jim, this isn't exactly a turn- on.
女生喜欢的是有自信的男生
I mean, girls like a guy with confidence.
有 当然有
Hey, I'm confident.
我有自信的不得了
Oh, I am... I'm absolutely, totally confident.
- 脱衣服吧 - 好
- Let's get naked. - Okay.
记得大一放暑假 我爸来接我
Seems like just yesterday my dad picked me up after my first year at college.
我们干了几罐啤酒
We popped a couple of beers...
然后他对我说 你是大人了
and he said, ''Now, you're a man.''
今天轮到我跟儿子说同样的话
And today I get to say the same thing to my son.
你的话只会让他尴尬
Honey, your speeches embarrass him.
拜托你酷一点 千万别鸡婆
So, try and do what the kids say, and just be cool.
我怎么可能不够酷
I think I bring new meaning to the word ''cool,'' honey.
前面就是他的宿舍
That's his dormitory up ahead.
换位置
Turn over.
- 宿舍不准带酒 - 好
- Can't bring alcohol in the dorms. - Good.
我只是想给我儿子吉姆一个惊喜
Thank you, Matt. I'm just here to surprise my son Jim.
- 把我的腿抬高 - 什么?
- Now pin my leg up. - What?
把我腿抬起来 像这样
Pin my leg up, like this.
也许你可以帮个忙
Maybe you can help me out, you know.
是这里吗?不是
Is that the one? No.
对了
There!
我现在记得了
Now I remember.
下不为例
I didn't do this for you.
谢了 老兄
Thanks, dude.
- 我的宝贝儿子呢? - 天哪
- Where's my big guy? - Oh, my God!
- 老天爷 - 吉姆 我们来早了
- Jesus! - Jim, we got here a little early.
- 爸 出去 - 我到车上等你
- Dad, get out! - I'll wait in the car.
快出去
Go, Dad! Oh, my...
- 天哪 - 那是你爸?
- Geez! - Was that your dad?
- 对不起 - 其实你知道
- I'm so sorry. - For your own edification...
这没什么好丢脸
son, I'm not embarrassed.
才怪
I am!
这是很正常的事
It's a perfectly normal thing for two...
- 人都有需要 - 爸 你要干嘛
- human beings to do. - Dad, what are you doing?
这就是人性
This is human nature... human nature at its best.
大家都做 你妈和我...现在是比较少
Son, everybody does it. Your mother and I... Well, not so much anymore.
你最喜欢的派 他们在床上
Got your favorite. Oh, my God! They're fucking!
老婆 冷静点 我最好带她...
Honey, honey, listen. I'm gonna take her...
- 快走啊！ - 拜托你们
- Please just go! - Actually, if you wouldn't mind.
老婆 我带她回车上去
Honey... I'll take her to the car.
- 嗨 妈 - 什么?
- Hi, Mama. - What?
娜塔莉
Natalie!
我是吉姆的父亲
I'm Jim's dad.
这位一定是你们的女儿
You must be the parents of this young lady.
我还不知道她的名字 不过我儿子一定知道
I'm sorry I didn't get her name, but hopefully my son did...
因为我也是刚到 因为我也是刚到
because I have not been here the whole time. because I have not been here the whole time.
娜塔莉 还不穿衣服
Natalie, get dressed!
- 要啤酒吗? - 转过去 不准看
- Beer? - Avert your eyes! Turn around!
- 吉姆 真是谢谢你 - 天哪
- Thanks,Jim. Don't believe in locks? - Oh, my God!
《美国派2》
(娘娘腔)
嗨 猪头
Hey, fuckface.
- 早啊 老兄 - 走吧 欧兹 上课了
- Mornin', dude. - Come on, Ozzy. It's show time.
在你去接海瑟之前
Before you go to Ann Arbor to pick up Heather...
我要你知道你错过了什么
I wanna show you what you're missing.
看她今天穿什么
See what they are today, dude. See what they are today.
准备好 答案要揭晓了
Okay, here we go. Moment of truth.
- 她穿有红心的内裤 - 炫哦
- There's little hearts on her panties! - Super.
她穿有红心的内裤 快看啊
There's little hearts on her panties! Come on, look, you pussy. Look.
搞什么?干嘛不看
What the fuck, man? Come on!
我对你太失望了
I'm disappointed in you.
到现在你才上过一个女的
Here it is, the end of our freshman year and you screwed one girl.
才一个
One.
你是我们男性的耻辱
You're a disgrace to men everywhere.
你看我 一上大一就做了23次
Look at the Stifmeister. I got laid 23 times this year...
而且图书馆那次还不算
and I'm not counting the hummer I got in the library stacks, baby.
你为什么不学我?
All right, here's a new idea for you, Stifler, okay?
交一个要好的女朋友
You find a girl. You two become best friends.
就不用数自己做过多少次
You don't bother counting how many times you have sex with each other.
- 还可以笑那些数的人 - 我有个建议
- You laugh at the people who do count. - Here's a new idea for you.
你怎么不去死
I'll get you a spoon so you can eat my ass.
好了 请把所有书本收起来 要开始考试了
Okay, people, notebooks closed. Let's get this exam rolling.
不是吧 我怎么不记得今天有要考试
Oh, shit! Do we got an exam today?
- 你不是这么夸张吧 - 完了
- Are you kiddin' me? - Bullshit.
终于不用再碰政治学了
Yes! I'm never even gonna think about political science again.
考得怎样?
Hey. How'd you do?
- 还好 - 是吗?
- Fine. - Yeah?
早知道就不参加游学了
I can't believe I'm doing the summer abroad. Last thing I need, more classes.
- 会很好玩的 - 考完了
- You're gonna have a great time. - Hello, summer!
- 难考吧? - 难得要命
- Did that exam blow or what? - Yeah, it sucked.
- 怎么样? - 还好
- Kev, what's up, man? How are you? - Good.
放暑假了
Put your party hat on.
- 有十二个礼拜大玩特玩 - 没错
- We got 12 weeks of immortality ahead. - Yes, sir!
好怪
Weird.
在想跑掉的那个?
The one that got away, huh, son?
你们两个在网路上看起来是很配
Well, evidently you two made quite the handsome couple on the Internet.
我没看到
I didn't see it.
别人在家长会上说的
It was brought up at a PTA meeting.
我的意思是
Anyway, my point is...
不要因为一点挫折就失去了信心
these little sexual debacles should not get you down, because you know what?
谁没第一次
It happens to the best of us.
老实说...
In fact...
你妈和我第一次...
the first time your mother and I...
在一起
got together...
我准备了保险套
I used a condom.
她居然说 像扁掉的气球
Well, she referred to it as ''shrink wrapping.''
但是我不在意
But I got over it.
只要不气馁 再接再励
Anyway, keep your chin up. You keep plugging...
总有成功的一天
and good things will happen.
欢迎你回家
Good to have you home, son.
回家真好
It's good to be home, Dad.
今晚史勒家一定很热闹
It's gonna be nice to hit Stifler's tonight after exams.
- 找到他们没? - 看是谁来了
- Did you get through 'em? - There's the mystery man!
你好吗?芬奇
Finch, how are you?
那是日语
It's Japanese.
意思是 你好 你好
It means ''hello.'' Hello.
- 你不学拉丁语啦? - 我在美术馆认识了一个日本妹
- Finch, what happened to Latin? - Met a Japanese girl at the art museum.
决定转系 想知道她呻吟些什么
Changed majors. Wanted to understand all those things she was moaning.
- 你在美术馆做过? - 是大都会美术馆
- You got laid in an art museum? - The Met.
- 跟法兰卡在古根汉美术馆 - 在古根汉?
- And the Guggenheim with Francesca. - The Guggenheim?
跟心理学教授是在31冰淇淋店
And then my social- psych professor in Baskin- Robbins.
够了 别说了
All right, enough.
可是我告诉你 没有人比得上...
But I'll tell you, none of these women even compare to...
史勒的妈妈
Stifler's mom.
他妈妈是人间极品
Stifler's mom is a goddess.
还有谁要我的校园综合果汁?
How about some more of Stifmeister's collegiate concoction?
喝起来像酒 你想把我灌醉啊
This thing is like half alcohol. You're just trying to get me drunk.
怎么会呢?玛丽
Mary, would I do that?
- 我是克莉丝 - 克莉丝 对 好名字
- My name's Christy. - Christy, right. Beautiful name.
管你叫什么
Like it matters.
怎么样啊?
Hey, how you doing?
好吗?死人头
Howdy- howdy, fuckin' partners!
强尼 不错吧 慢慢玩
Johnny C., how's it going? Good to see you.
怎么有个欧巴桑混进来
Looks like someone gained the freshman 15.
- 别吓人了 - 你这个烂人
- This'll help. - You're an asshole.
不客气
Missed you too.
玩得高兴吗?各位
All right, everybody having a good time? Ladies.
你们来啦 欢迎
Fellas! How's it going?
饮料在后面 自己拿
The keg's back there as always. Enjoy.
你们好 我是史勒 我的弟弟长11英寸
Ladies, I'm Steve Stifler and I have an 11-inch penis...
直径哦
around!
考虑一下 雪门
Think about it. Sherman!
行了 史勒 别假了
Okay, Stifler, take your shot.
我是真的很高兴看到你
Come on, man. I'm really happy to see you.
好耶
All right.
你这个白痴
You stupid fuck!
- 你是史帝夫史勒吗? - 正是在下
- Are you Steve Stifler? - Yes, I am.
谢谢你举办这么炫的派对
Thank you for throwing this awesome party, man.
- 小事一件 - 我们每次办舞会都有条子来找碴
- No problem. - The cops bust all our parties now.
我特地放话去找了一堆高中美眉
Well, I put the word out so high school chicks would come.
不过这并不代表 我也欢迎你们这种高中逊炮弟
Just 'cause you fuckers don't have dicks doesn't make it okay for you to be here.
- 我可以问你一个问题吗? - 请问
- Hey, could I ask you a question? - Sure, son.
保罗芬奇真的上过你妈吗?
Is it true that Paul Finch nailed your mom?
死人头
Sons of bitches.
我妈才不是那种女人
My mom's a saint!
那是芬奇乱掰的
Go choke some dick!
嗨 卡罗 杰森
Hey, Carlos,Jason.
你们好吗?啤酒在后面阳台上
What's goin' on? Keg's back on the deck.
爱荷华大学怎么样?
How was Iowa State?
你们看到现在小鬼 有多没规矩了吗?
Did you see those fuckers I had to boot out of here?
还是跟以前一样
Back at Stifler's. Just like old times.
有一点不一样
One difference.
我们现在是大学生
We're college men now.
可是这里有些女生还在念高中
Some of these girls are from the grade below us.
这样我就有机会了
I might actually have a chance.
我认得你
Hey, I remember you.
是吗?
Do you now?
你是网路上那个逊炮
You're that guy who blew his load on the Internet.
还一边喊 娜迪雅 不要走
Splat. ''Oh, wait, Nadia, don't go.'' Splat.
- 差劲 - 逊毙了
- Pathetic. - Loser.
真的是跟以前一样
It's exactly like old times.
(东大瀑布机场)
- 我会想你的 - 我也是
- I'm gonna miss you. - I'll miss you.
我到了就打电话给你
I'll call you when I get in, okay?
好好玩
Go have fun.
再见
Bye.
那两个女的实在很坏 那两个女的实在很坏
I can't believe those two girls, Kevin. I can't believe those two girls, Kevin.
有什么大不了的
Jim, it's not a big deal.
她们玩弄我的感情
They toyed with my emotions.
- 你好 - 看吧 妹妹多的是
- Hello. Hello. - See? There's other girls.
- 你好吗? - 有什么好怕的
- How are you? - You got nothing to worry about, man.
洁西卡也在
Jessica's here.
跟维琪一起
With Vicky.
维琪很哈哦
And Vicky got hot!
什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
你自己看
Look at her.
- 我看到了 - 嗨 凯文
- Yeah,Jim, I see her. - Hey, Kevin.
我过去一下
I'll be right back.
- 你好吗?维琪 - 怎么样?
- Hey, Vic, how are you? - What's up?
- 还不错 - 我很好
- I'm okay. - Yeah, I'm good.
那就好
That's good.
- 那就好 - 对啊
- It's good to hear. - Yeah, you too.
哇 气氛有够尴尬的
Wow. Well, this is about as comfortable as a high colonic in Tijuana.
连我都看得出来
And I would know. Okay.
- 我去拿饮料 - 她说得对
- I'm gonna get a drink. - She's right.
- 为什么会这么怪? - 我也不知道
- Why is this so weird? - Actually, I have no idea.
我就知道 你不会那么不成熟
See, I knew it. I knew you'd be mature about this.
至少我们还可以做朋友
You know, and we could still be friends, right?
凯文 我想念你
I miss you, Kev.
不是吧
Whoa.
是朋友吧?
Friends, right?
当然是 我知道你的意思
Yeah, right. I mean, I know you said friends and I... I just...
对不起 我只是...
I'm sorry. I was... It was just...
一时忘记 亲你亲习惯了
an old habit... a friend kiss.
你确定?
Are you sure?
我怎么会不愿意跟你做朋友?
Vic, why wouldn't I wanna be friends with you?
不如 我们先握手好了
Look, we'll... we'll just do this, okay?
- 朋友 - 朋友
- Friends. - Friends.
- 欧兹 兄弟 - 他在那里
- Ozzy, my man! - There he is.
准备要加入我们 炮友俱乐部了吗?
Shake off your chains of monogamy? You're a free man.
多谢你的好意 史勒 但我是不会跟你同流合污的
I don't think so, Stifler. I'll never turn over to the dark side.
少装了 当年那个情圣到那去了
Dumb ass. What happened to the Nova I knew in high school?
你那时可是我们 高中的校园之狼耶
Nova, as in Casanova, the guy who had all the moves.
- 我早已退出江湖 - 你那时可是我的偶像耶
- He was an idiot. - Yeah, but he was my idiot.
大家听好
Hey, everyone, listen up!
校园之狼今夜将重出江湖
Nova's back, baby...
因为他终于挣脱了他的贞操带
and he's taken the lock off his cock!
欧兹 我帮你找个好上手的
Ozzy, I'm lobbing you a softball.
把小弟弟准备好 要上场了
Pull out your bat and take a swing.
曼蒂
Mandy.
这是我的朋友 欧兹 蝉联两年的长曲棍球州冠军
This is my friend, Oz. All- state lacrosse two years running.
- 嗨 欧兹 - 曼蒂 你好
- Hi, Oz. - Mandy, how are you?
很高兴能认识你
Listen. I have a girlfriend.
可惜我已经有女朋友了
It was a pleasure meeting you.
啤酒在后面是吧
Beer out back.
你这个孬种
You pussy!
史勒妈妈的房间
Stifler's mom's room.
你为什么那么厉害?
How did you do that magic you did?
印度教
Tantra.
你躲在这边干嘛?
What the fuck are you doin' in here?
- 别紧张 - 你给我滚出去
- Just relax. - You get out of my house!
- 妈呀 - 有种给我回来
- Jesus Christ! - Come back here, you little fucker!
- 回来 你这个混蛋 - 别这样
- Come back here, you son of a bitch! - Take it easy.
好了 别吵了
Easy! Easy! That's enough.
去年夏天已经吵过了
Okay, guys, we went through this last summer, all right?
芬奇眼睛黑了一圈 史勒缝了六针
Finch got a black eye and Stifler got six stitches.
因为他咬我
'Cause he fuckin' bit me!
你敢碰我 我再咬
You touch me, I bite.
- 你们两个握手 别吵了 - 握你个头
- You two relax and shake hands. - Shake this.
我要去喝一杯
I need a drink.
大家干嘛都选在这个时候尿尿?
Why is everybody taking a piss right now?
- 这么多人 我憋不住了 - 你可以的 别念了
- Line's too long. I ain't gonna make it. - You'll be okay. Relax.
你就是那个跟史勒妈妈上床的人
Hey, bro. Hey, man, you're the guy who boned Stifler's mom.
- 天啊 你太帅了 - 偶像
- Hey, you are a god. - Holy shit, dude.
我要不是怕尿出来 一定跟你握手
If I didn't have to hold my dick 'cause I gotta piss, I would shake your hand.
- 多谢夸奖 - 别走
- I'm honored, guys. - Don't leave.
你得教我 怎么做的
You must teach me. How?
怎么做的?
How?
克莉丝 看我找到什么
Look what I found, Christy.
这么巧
What a coincidence.
这是为了特殊的场合
I've been saving this for a special occasion...
和你这样特别的女孩准备的
for a special girl, just like you.
- 你真可爱 - 大家都这么说
- You're so sweet. - That's what they say.
奇怪
Weird.
- 糟糕 - 洒到你身上了
- Oh, my God. - I spilled some on you.
- 我帮你擦干净 - 谢谢
- Maybe I should mop that up. - Thanks.
别客气
No problem.
等一下
Whoa! Whoa, hey.
- 别急嘛 - 对
- Take it slow. Come on. - Right.
学校警告过我们这种情况
You know, they warn us about these situations in college.
也许你喝醉了
Now, you may be intoxicated.
对吧
Oh, yeah.
你确定你愿意和我发生...
Are you certain that you wish to engage in consenting...
你那么猴急干嘛
Hey, don't count your chickens, buster.
- 我只是照规矩来 - 照我的规矩
- I'm just playing by the rules, baby. - I make the rules.
这种规矩 我喜欢
That's a pretty good fucking rule.
队伍太长 我憋不住了
Dude, the line's too long. I'll never make it.
- 我要尿了 帮我看着 - 尿吧
- It's gotta happen now. Get my back. - Go, bro.
- 等一下 - 哈罗
- Clamp it off. - Hello.
- 你好吗? - 好极了
- How are you? - Awesome.
- 你好吗? - 我很好
- How are you? - I'm really good.
要不要来点香槟?
How 'bout I give you a little champagne?
可不可以帮我们拿几罐啤酒?
Go downstairs and get us some beers?
眼睛闭起来 有个惊喜给你
I've got a surprise for you. Close your eyes and get ready.
闭好了
I'm ready.
- 你要啤酒吗? - 要 谢谢
- You want a beer? - Yeah, all right.
可以了
Okay, go.
有点怪 但是我喜欢
This is kind of kinky, and I like that.
太棒了 香槟浴
That's it. Bathe the Stifmeister.
好舒服
Oh, that's great!
That's great.
你怎么把香槟弄温的
How did you get it so nice and warm?
还可以喝到泡泡
I can taste the bubbles.
怎么喝不到
Actually, I can't.
舒服多了
Much better.
等一下
Wait a second.
- 走吧 - 谢了 老兄
- Let's go. - Thanks, man.
天哪
Oh, fuck!
(东方高中学生停车证)
这里有一半以上的车 有帖东方高中的学生停车证
Yep. Half these got East High parking passes on them.
看来我们得去取缔一下 叫总局派人来支援
Gotta break up another one. Call in a couple of units.
- 那不是史勒的房子吗? - 是啊 你见过史勒太太吗?
- Isn't this the Stifler house? - Yeah. Ever seen Ms. Stifler?
- 真是人间尤物 - 是吗?她有那么辣?
- What a MI LF! - Yeah? She got all that?
你们想...
Okay, now...
这群高中生会认为 我们是大学派对的酷哥
do these high schoolers think we're cool because they're at a college party...
还是那些放假回家
or are we those weird older guys...
混高中舞会的怪老头
that try to hang out with high school kids when we come home?
不可能 怎么可能是我们
No way. We're definitely not those guys.
条子来了
Cops! Cops!
派对结束了 散会
Break it up. Party's over.
走吧
Let's go.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
史帝夫史勒呢?
Where's Steve Stifler?
我被尿了一身
I got peed on.
不是 派对被解散
No, man, Stifler's got shut down.
还不准我们再开
We can't party anywhere anymore.
而且感觉...
And things are...
- 怪怪的? - 是有一点
- Getting weird? - Yeah, a little bit.
大学第一个暑假
First summer back from college.
感觉会越来越怪
Yep, things are gonna get weirder.
- 什么意思? - 时间在变 人也在变
- What are you talkin' about? - Well, times change, people change.
这就是人生
It's just what happens, you know.
凯文 去我以前的房间
Kev, listen. Go into my old room.
我跟我朋友都觉得要保持联络
My friends and I knew that it was up to us to stick together.
记得大一放暑假 我们在大港租了间渡假屋
You remember my first college summer? We rented that lake house in Grand Harbor.
每天都像在开高中毕业舞会
We treated every day out there like it was a post- prom party.
玩得比高中的时候还疯
Hell of a time. We capped it all off with a massive blowout.
这辈子最棒的暑假
Best ever. It was legendary.
你也应该这样 等到放完假
My advice is do that. By the end of the summer...
你就明白了
you're gonna see the big picture.
(阿姆与牙齿历险记)
- 她打来了 是长途电话 - 谁打来了?
- She's on the phone. It's long distance. - Who?
- 娜迪雅 她打来了 - 什么?
- Nadia! Nadia! - What?
从纽约 喂 他就在旁边
New York. Hello. Yes, dear, he's right here.
- 快给我 - 记住...
- Here. Wait. - Now remember...
我一定会去看《狮子王》
Yes, I am sure to go see the Lion King.
还有不要半夜一个人搭地铁
Right. And don't ride the subway after midnight.
虽然他们有整顿纽约 但是...
I know they've done wonderful things with that city, but, you know, for me...
- 爸 - 他在旁边 等一下
- Dad! - He's right... Hang on.
- 大学生活如何? - 很棒
- How was college? - College was excellent.
嗯...非常棒
Yeah. Yeah, it was... it was really excellent.
你不是忘了我吧?
You have not forgotten about me, have you?
不是...当然不是
No. I... Absolutely not.
- 我当然没忘 - 那就太好了 知道吗
- I definitely didn't. - Good, because guess what.
暑假结束前我会去看你
I'm coming to see you at the end of summer.
希望你做好准备
I hope you're ready for me...
因为我也没忘记你 帅哥
because I have not forgotten about you either,you sexy boy.
- 妈的 - 吉姆 你可以明天再来吃
- Shit. - Jim, you can eat hot dogs tomorrow.
不 芬奇 跟餐厅没关系
No, Finch, it's not the hot dogs.
娜迪雅今天早上打来
Nadia called me this morning.
说暑假结束前要来看我
She's coming here at the end of the summer and she wants to see me.
- 那很棒啊 - 那不是很好
- That's killer. - Yeah, that's a good thing.
错了 才不好 完全不棒
No, not ''good thing.'' Not ''killer.''
我根本办不到
I'll never be able to do it.
她希望我能变成猛男
Nadia is gonna be expecting filet mignon.
偏偏我只能变成...
Okay, and all I'm gonna be able to give her...
逊炮
is rump roast.
别这样 你之后也有过别的经验
Come on.Jim, you've had experience since Nadia.
是哦 如果你是指
Ah, yes, you would be referring to...
那个虐待完 又抛弃我的变态乐队女
the flute- fetish band geek that made me her bitch, then ditched me after prom.
那是了不起的经验 就是那次
Yes, that's great experience.
阿姆 只要你找到合适的女孩
You just gotta find the right girl,Jimbo.
- 马上就搞定 - 我找到了
- Brings it all together. - I had the right woman.
可惜她卖掉房子 躲了起来
She just sells her cottage and takes off to parts unknown.
我的感情生活完了
My romantic life has passed its peak.
让我死了吧
Take me out to the pasture and shoot me.
这就是我们的暑假 欢迎回来
Super start to a super summer, fellas. Welcome home.
喂 我有个好主意 我们走吧
Guys, I got it. Pack your bags.
去哪?
For what?
准备出发去湖边
We're moving to the lake.
沙滩上每个人都会认识我们
We're gonna be the shit. Everybody on the beach is gonna know us.
还可以找到一堆练习的对象
Plenty of opportunities to practice for Nadia.
暑假结束前办场盛大的狂欢派对
Throw a huge party at the end of the summer to cap it all off.
这个主意好 可以帮海瑟洗尘
Dude, that's a great idea. That way we'll be able to welcome Heather back...
还可以帮娜迪雅接风
and we'll be able to prepare for Nadia's big arrival.
这就对了 我的恋爱暑假
This is it. This is my summer of love.
我是来跟你们说再见的
Just thought I'd say good- bye to you animals.
嗨 伯父 你好
Hey, Mr. Levenstein. How are you, sir?
- 看样子都准备好了 - 对 我们准备好了
- All packed up, I see. - We're all set, Dad.
别担心 我不会有事的
Don't worry, okay? I'll be fine.
过来抱你老爸一下
Come on and give your old man a hug.
别玩太疯哦
Keep it real, homies.
您也一样 有个愉快的暑假
You too, sir. Have a good summer.
好了 我们走吧
All right, let's go.
我算过 我们四个绝对负担不起
I've been running these numbers and the four of us can't afford this place.
就算有暑期工
Not on summer jobs.
这个 我已经想到了
Well, I kind of thought of that.
所以 我还多找了一个人
So, I invited someone else.
注意 世纪大猛男来大港了
Oh, yeah! The Stifmeister's coming back to Grand Harbor!
快点出来列队欢迎
Deck the halls! Bye- bye, Great Falls!
保证看到你口水直流
Wipe my ass and lick my balls!
世纪大猛男来啦
It's Stifler time, baby!
史勒 拜托你稍微控制一下
Stifler, if you're gonna be living with us, you gotta behave yourself.
还有 要跟芬奇和平相处
All right, you and Finch just stay out of each other's way.
凯文 他天生就秀逗
Kevin, Stifler's stench is unavoidable.
你去吃屎吧你
Finch, fist yourself.
辣妹 我们来啦
That's right, baby. We're here.
帅哥在这里
Yeah, baby, we're here!
- 好气派 - 好庄严
- It's a palace. - It's a temple.
是不是很棒?
Isn't this great?
- 天啊 - 不是盖的
- Dude. - Are you kidding me?
设计错误
This just won't do.
(征暑期油漆工读大专生)
喂
Guys.
你们看 找到了
Check this out. This is it.
谁能告诉我这个白痴在干嘛
Will you idiots tell me what this fucker's doin'?
我灵修的时候别碰我
Don't touch me while I'm tantric.
灵修?那是什么狗屁?
''Tantric?'' What the fuck is tantric?
是密宗的修行方式
It's a Buddhist discipline.
练习沟通体内的能量 就是灵性
You learn to channel your body's energies... your chakras.
只要能入定 就能达到灵肉合一的境界
When you can do that, you can have sex for hours, even days.
真的假的?
And this stuff's for real?
流传好几个世纪了
It's been around for centuries.
灵修可以让你的性感区
With tantra you can make an entire session of sex...
感受到前所未有的高潮
feel like one giant orgasm.
最后只要靠灵修就可以维持快感
Eventually, you can sustain that feeling by meditating.
- 可以教我吗? - 我怀疑
- Maybe you can teach me sometime? - Very doubtful.
- 也对 - 吉姆 少驴了
- True. - Come on,Jim.
- 你不可能那么逊 - 是吗?
- You can't possibly be that bad. - Oh, no?
不可能
No way.
这个答案只有一个人知道
I guess there's only one person that really knows for sure, huh?
真的?那她人在哪?
Oh, yeah? Where is she this summer?
(巨橡乐队营)
你是来看表演的吗?
Hey, are you here for the mid- session performance?
你来错地方了 应该去剧场
Guests go in the amphitheater. You can't be here.
你知道蜜雪儿哈提在哪吗?
Do you know where I could find Michelle Flaherty?
观众带食物进场 食物引来动物
Guests bring food. Food attracts animals. This one time...
有次还引来一头熊 熊最后被杀掉
a bear came, and then the bear had to be destroyed...
是被人用来福枪打中头部死的
which means they shot it in the head with a rifle and killed it and it died.
你一定认识蜜雪儿
You must know Michelle.
一、二、三、四
One, two, three, four.
是一堆长笛
That's a lot of flutes.
再见 谢谢
Good luck. Thanks.
吹得好 去上下一堂课吧
Good job. Have fun at your next class.
吉姆 我的天哪
Jim. Holy potatoes!
- 你怎么来了? - 不要走散
- You're really here? - Everybody stick together.
糟了
Oh, shoot!
这里不准有访客的
We're not supposed to have visitors...
因为有一次
'cause this one time, here...
有个小鬼带了饼干来...
this kid had these cookies... this kid had these cookies...
让我猜 引来一头熊
Let me guess. A bear came.
厉害
Cool.
我们的事你好像都知道
It's like you know all our stories.
那是一个问题吗?
Was that a question?
也许吧 我不知道
I don't know. Maybe.
你想回答吗?
Do you wanna answer it anyway?
毕业舞会后 我留了三次话给你
I left you like... like three messages after prom.
真的?
Really?
你不觉得我那天晚上表现得很怪
You didn't think I was weird because of the way I acted that night?
怪 不会
Weird, no.
讶异 会
Surprising, yes.
我饥渴的时候就会那样
I get nasty when I'm horny.
我来就是为了那件事
That's kind of why I'm here.
我那天晚上表现得如何?
You remember, was I any good that night?
天哪
Wow. Geez.
我怎么可能忘记?
How could I forget?
逊毙了 你根本不知道该怎么做
You sucked. You didn't know what the hell you were doing.
虽然你很逊 还是满有意思的
But wasn't it fun even though you were so terrible?
- 你说什么?很逊? - 我还碰过更逊的
- I'm sorry. ''Terrible?'' - I've had worse.
对不起
Sorry.
你要的话 我可以教你
I could give you some pointers if you want.
真的?
Really?
糟了 等我一下 给我一个小时
Shoot. Okay, wait here. I'll meet you in an hour, okay?
- 好 - 等一下
- Yeah. - Wait.
我想到了
Cool idea.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
你没事吧?你怎么还在这里
You're all right. Here we go. You know you're not supposed to be here now.
大家都去剧场集合了 快点
Everyone's supposed to be in the amphitheater. All right, come on.
我非常生气 你居然敢迟到
It's piss poor to be this late. I'm very angry right now.
听我的声音就听得出来
You can tell by the tone of my voice I'm angry. I'm pissed off is what I am.
- 他们在那边 让他进去 - 还不快进去
- Here they are. Got him home. - Go, go.
等一下 你是皮迪
Wait a minute. Are you Petey?
对
Yeah, sure.
你是皮迪 那就难怪
Petey! Well, that explains everything.
这些小鬼老是会出一些状况
All right. Well, always something with these kids. Go!
我们实在很高兴你能来 这边的学生哪能跟你比
We are just so thrilled to have you. None of my kids are at your caliber.
你能来 我们实在是太高兴了
But we are just so overjoyed to have someone with your kind of talent here.
- 太好了 - 拿着
- Great. - Here you go.
你看 你的老搭档
Look at this. Your old best friend.
- 去吧 - 虽然这不是你自己的
- Come on. Move. - I know it's not yours...
但是以你的技术绝对没问题
but you are going to make beautiful music.
- 去吧 - 实在是太棒了
- Here we go. - This is fantastic. I'm very excited.
放心大胆的表演吧
You just own this and break a leg.
好耶
Yeah.
他干嘛一个人在外面闲晃?
What was he doing wandering unsupervised?
谁晓得?
Who knows?
告诉你 我受够这群智障儿了
I'll tell you something. I'm about fed up with these Tall Oaks North kids.
(巨橡智能障碍乐团)
小朋友们 跟着皮迪吹
Kids, entertain yourselves. Play along with Petey.
不对 皮迪 是这边
No, no, no, Petey. Here we go.
好了 大家给他一点鼓励
All right, all right. Come on, now. A little encouragement.
“嘉宾皮迪: 伸缩喇叭独奏” 你站这边
Right to this spot.
各位 他只是有点紧张
Folks, he's just a little nervous.
你弄错了
This isn't right.
没错 你吹就对了
Just blow on it, kid. All right.
开始吧
Here we go.
皮迪 开始啊
Come on, Petey.
吹啊 别光站着
Play! Do something.
嘉宾个屁
Special, my ass.
我们大家给他一点鼓励
Come on. Give the little guy some support.
加油 皮迪 你没问题的
Come on, Petey. You're doing great, partner.
加油 你做得到的
Come on, honey. You can do it.
皮迪 加油
Come on, Petey.
管他的
What the hell.
好耶
All right!
好耶 加油 皮迪
All right, Petey! Come on, now! Come on!
我来啦
Rock and roll!
谢谢
Thank you!
谢谢大家 你们真好
Thank you, Tall Oaks. You're beautiful.
我叫皮迪
My name is Petey!
谢谢大家
Thank you!
我的蛋蛋最大
And I have gigantic balls!
别闹了 等下再说
Not now! Come back later. Go!
你 你给我回来
Hey, hey, hey. Come back here!
- 我有话跟你说 - 你人真好
- I wanna talk to you! - You are so sweet.
他有够特别的
He is special.
他是我马子
He's my bitch.
我已经跟蜜雪儿证实过了
Well, Michelle has confirmed it.
- 我逊毙了 - 什么?
- I suck. - What?
我需要多加练习
I gotta get some practice.
别担心 这间渡假屋不是白租的
Don't worry about it. I mean, that's why we got the house,Jimbo.
在阳台上准备一堆饮料 保证引来一群辣妹
We plop a keg on the deck and the girls come in off the beach.
就像蜜蜂看到花一样
It's like a hummingbird feeder.
- 你确定? - 我确定
- You think so? - I know so.
保证有效
Guaranteed hotties.
老兄 不错嘛
Fellas, nice pad.
风景不错
Good view, but...
雪门终结者侦测到 附近没有女性生物
the Sherminator sensors detect no female life- forms in the vicinity.
极有可能演变成光棍聚会
High likelihood of a sausagefest in progress.
我打过电话了 妹妹很快就到
The girls are coming. I made some calls.
他说得对 凯文
The Sherminator's got a point, Kev.
你什么时候开始信他的屁话的?
Since when do you start listening to the Sherminator?
自从我发现这边只有一票弟弟后
Since he made me realize there's an abundance of wiener here.
不信你自己看看
I mean, look around, dude. Dude?
好吧 轮到你了
All right, now it's your turn.
别闹了 没什么好说的
Come on. There's nothing to tell.
你们在干嘛?在聊什么?
Hey, what's up? What are you guys talking about?
没什么 只是在交换小道消息
Well, you know, we're just trading war stories about college...
谁跟谁交朋友 谁跟谁上床
who hooked up with who, who slept with who...
你呢?维琪
So, Vicky?
是有一个男的 你呢
Well, there was this one guy. How 'bout you?
有认识几个女的
You know, there was a few girls...
三个
three.
看不出来哦 泡妞高手
Look at you. You stud.
欧兹 凯文说完 轮到你了
All right, Oz. Now that Kevin told us, what about you?
学校没有让你动心的女孩吗?
You haven't had the slightest bit of attraction to any girl at school?
别给我说没有 我知道你有
Don't you fuckin' say no. I know you did.
就算我有
Even if I did...
也只是一时的冲动
it wouldn't be anything more than just a momentary thing.
有够无聊
Very uninteresting.
洁西卡呢?今年上了几个妹妹
How about you,Jessica? How many chicks did you sleep with this year?
你那么想知道
Gee, wouldn't you like to know.
这还用问
Fuck yeah I would.
走吧 欧兹
Come on, Ozzy.
好 去玩球 你们打撞球吧
Yeah, man. Ball. Pool's yours.
- 维琪 要不要打 - 好啊 你来开球
- Hey, Vic, you wanna play? - Yeah, sure. You wanna break?
搞什么
What the...
妹妹跑哪去了?
Where are the fuckin' females?
拜托你把衣服穿上 妹妹都被你吓跑了
Jim, can't you leave your shirt on? You're scaring the chicks away.
别烦我 行不行
Dude, give him a break.
欧兹 下去接球
Ozzy, go deep.
你要玩吗?
Yeah, bro. You playing?
再往后 侧攻
No, keep going. Flank pattern.
- 你要干嘛? - 钓马子
- What are you doin'? - Fishin'.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
- 你还好吧? - 真对不起 你们没事吧
- You okay? - I'm so sorry. Is everybody okay?
厉害
Amazing.
这招最有效
The Force is strong in that one.
哇哦
Whoa.
雪门终结者侦测到前方有热源
The Sherminator detects serious heat at a distance of two meters.
准备部署啤酒
Prepare to deploy beer.
让我给你一个良心的建议
Dude, let me give you a valuable piece of advice, okay?
少来“雪门终结者” 这一套
Drop the whole ''Sherminator'' thing.
请重覆之前谈话
Please repeat previous statement.
我知道你叫雪门
Look, I know your last name is Sherman, right?
再加上十年前轰动的电影《魔鬼终结者》
And that rhymes with The Terminator which was a big hit movie ten years ago.
你不是以为女生会吃你这套吧
But you can't tell me a girl's ever really gone for it.
系统超载 再会 洁西卡
System overload. Hasta la vista, Jessica.
怪胎
Freak.
维琪 你们要走啦
Vic, hey, you guys are leaving?
我们还没机会好好聊一聊
You know, we barely had a chance to hang out, you know, catch up.
- 你这周末要干嘛? - 没干嘛
- What are you doing this weekend? - I can get together.
- 那就一块出去吧 - 好啊
- Cool. Let's hang out. - All right.
- 再见 凯文 - 再见 洁西卡
- Bye, Kev. - See ya,Jess.
错了 这不适合你
No, no, that's all wrong.
- 谢谢 下次再来 - 再见
- Thank you. Have a nice day. - Good-bye.
- 他的“碰面”是什么意思 - 就是一块出去
- So what does he mean, ''meet up''? - You know, like hang out...
吃个饭什么的
grab lunch, whatever.
我跟他只是普通朋友 他知道的
I told you, we're just friends now. And he totally understands.
- 我怀疑他知道吗 - 他当然知道
- I'm sure he understands quite well. - He does.
先生 这些完全不适合你 真的
Oh, no, sir. These are all wrong for you. I mean, seriously.
我们只是朋友
Sure. Well, we're friends.
但也不表示我完全没机会
But it's not like I see her making plans with anyone else.
至少她目前还没男朋友
I don't see her with a boyfriend. I think that puts me on deck.
我之后 她只跟一个男的上过床
Hey, Vicky only slept with one guy since we went out.
换言之 我占有百分之五十的地位
I mean, that like makes me 50% of her entire guy- related life.
你放屁
You dipshit.
她不只跟一个 最少跟过三个
She didn't sleep with one guy. She slept with at least three.
什么?
What?
女生告诉你跟几个男的
When a girl tells you how many guys she slept with...
通常要乘以三 才是正确的数目
multiply it by three and that's the real number.
你们这群白痴 大学上假的啊
Didn't you fuckers learn anything at college?
他不可能有上过三个女的 这就好比我告诉你说...
He did not sleep with three girls, much like Sly and the Family Stone...
我跟四大天王都有一腿
aren't gonna dance in here and gang- bang me...
你用膝盖想都知道是假的
between the afros and the bell- bottoms.
根本就太扯了嘛
It's not gonna happen.
- 凯文才没上到三个那么多 - 他干嘛要骗我?
- Kevin did not sleep with three girls. - Why would he lie to me?
不是骗 是修饰 三倍定律 不是骗 是修饰 三倍定律
It's not a lie. It's an adjustment. The rule of three. It's not a lie. It's an adjustment. The rule of three.
- 什么定律? - 三倍
- The rule of what? - Three.
男生都会夸大做过的数目
A guy tells you how many girls he's been with, it's not even close to that.
只要把他说的除以三 就对了
Take that number and divide it by three. Then you get the real total.
他说三个 搞不好连一个都没有
So, if Kevin's saying it's been three girls, it's more like one, or none.
- 没有? - 三倍定律
- None? - Rule of three.
永恒不变的定律
It's an exact science, consistent as gravity.
欧兹 我真替你高兴
Ozzy, I'm happy for you.
虽然海瑟在欧洲大吹喇叭 但你至少在这里也大饱眼福
At least you've seen a nice bod while Heather's off suckin' dick.
你不需要跟我分享你的春梦
Keep your fantasies to yourself.
拜托你用你的常识好好想一想
Dude, use your fuckin' brain.
“我是美国纯情女大学生”
''I'm the American college chick. La, la, la.
“你们欧洲人的文化水平真高”
Your European cultural shit is so charming.
“你们西班牙男生真帅 讲话的口音真好听”
Hot Spanish guy. Love your accent.
“小弟弟也不错喔”
Love your ding- dong.''
我跟你打赌 你马子 现在一定正在帮人吹喇叭
I'm tellin' you, right now there is a dick in your girlfriend's mouth.
- 你给我闭嘴 - 我又没说什么
- Knock it off. - What'd I say?
我的天
Oh, my God!
你们 快看 女同志
Guys, check it out. Lesbians.
她们住在这里
Lesbians live here.
反同性恋专家
You know, Mr. Homophobic Wizard...
女生牵手不代表她们是同性恋
that it is possible for women to hold hands and not be gay.
朋友也可以牵手
Friends can hold hands.
我不想听你跟你男朋友的事 去自慰去
Hey, Finch, I don't wanna hear about you and your boyfriends. Go jerk off.
没那个必要
Unnecessary.
灵修的老师教我们
Tantra teaches you to hold an orgasm over time...
高潮要保留到最后一刻
in anticipation of an ultimate moment...
再尽情释放出来
to release it upon the world.
我已经准备好了
I'm filling up to the brim.
你有够恶心 我要吐了
That's fucking disgusting! I'm gonna throw up.
海瑟 你在家
Hey, Heather. You're in!
课上的怎样?
How's the studying going?
根本不像在上课
I'd hardly call it studying.
我们去博物馆参观 去教堂玩
I've been going to the Picasso Museum, hanging out at Sagrada Familia...
跟皮耶去公园
going with Pierre to the Parc Guell.
- 皮耶是谁? - 上课的同学
- Who's Pierre? - One of the guys in the program.
他女朋友在法国 跟我同病相怜
He's got a girlfriend back in France, so we've kind of got something in common.
那我就放心了
That sounds cool.
我无意中听到他们在通电话
Yeah, I've overheard them on the phone at night.
害我开始想要
And, well, it made me think.
欧兹 我正在摸我自己
Hey, Oz, I'm reaching under my shirt and I'm rubbing myself.
别这样 这是色情电话 来嘛
Oz, come on. It's phone sex. Help me out here.
好吧
Okay.
我走到床边
I'm going over to my bed.
躺下来
And I'm lying down.
把手慢慢地...
And I'm slowly...
伸进裤子里
reaching downstairs.
用力握住 告诉我有多粗
Grab it. Tell me how big it is.
海瑟 我觉得有点怪
Listen, Heather, I'm feeling kind of awkward.
就是因为分隔两地 才需要这样
If we can't be with each other, then we have to learn to be more vocal.
- 对不对? - 对
- Right? - Right. Okay.
好吧 我的手伸进了裤子
Okay, here we go. I'm reaching in my pants now.
我正在替你摸它
And I'm rubbing it for you, Heather.
感觉好舒服
And it feels so good.
- 我也是 - 快一点
- Yeah, me too. - Oh,yeah.
我...
I got...
有插播
Call waiting.
可恶 喂
Oh, shit. Hello?
你打错了
Wrong number.
喂 你打错了
Hey. Hello. Wrong number.
老兄 拜托 我正在自慰
All right, look, man. I got my hand on my dick right now, okay...
跟我女朋友讲色情电话
and I'm trying to have sex with my girlfriend over the phone.
真好
Good for you, man.
对不起 刚才到哪了
Sorry about that. Where were we?
你正在摸一样东西
I think you were reaching for something.
对
Oh, yeah.
哦 我正在摸我自己 好舒服
Oh, yeah, Heather. I'm rubbing it and it feels so good.
我也在摸我自己 有什么要求吗
Hey, Oz, I'm touching myself. What else do you want me to do?
海瑟 宝贝
Heather, baby.
告诉我 我的老二跟史勒一样大
Why don't you tell me my dick is as big as Stifler's.
史勒 快挂掉
Stifler, get off!
光听你们说话 就让我兴奋
I am getting off just listening to the two of you.
- 继续啊 - 我们下次再来好了
- Keep going. - We should try this another time.
好 再见 我爱你
Yeah, all right. Bye. I love you.
- 我也爱你 - 别这样 我快好了
- I love you. - Come on you, guys. I was almost there!
- 不跟你聊了 史帝夫 - 这个死人头
- Nice talking with you, Steven. - Stifler, man!
性压抑
Repressed.
你们看
Check it out.
女同志离开了
Potential lesbians leaving the building.
我的机会来了
All right. Now is my chance.
我要去求证
I need confirmation.
史勒 你要干嘛
Stifler. Hey, man, what are you doing?
快阻止他
Go get him.
混蛋 滚出来
You ass. Stifler, get out.
妈的 我找到情趣棒了
Shit, dude! I found a dildo!
老少咸宜的蓝色塑胶阳具
Big blue rubber dicks for everyone!
- 满足女性的需要 - 芬奇 快来帮忙
- The people demand rubber dicks! - Finch, help. Finch
情趣棒情趣棒
Dildo, dildo, dildo!
- 你在干嘛? - 找女同志的性玩具
- What are you doing? - Looking for more lesbian artifacts.
- 从哪找到的? - 芬奇的屁股
- Where'd you get this? - Finch's ass.
- 完了 - 糟了 她们回来了
- Oh, my God. - Shit! Guys, they're back.
拖住她们
Stall 'em!
快放回去
Come on. Come on!
- 动作快 - 有够刺激
- Come on. Come on. - This is awesome!
嗨 丹妮 安柏
Danielle, Amber, hi.
去买报纸?
Just needed the paper, huh?
- 哪个房间 - 我太兴奋 忘了
- Which room? - I can't remember. I was too excited.
- 我光顾着找证据 - 是不是这间?
- I'm in a lesbian stronghold. - Was it in here?
- 你问那么多干嘛? - 是不是这间?
- Why you asking me so many questions? - Was it in here?
- 好像是 - 到底是不是
- Maybe. - Was it or was it not here?
慢慢油漆吧
Happy painting, boys.
快出来 她们进去了
You gotta get out of there. They're inside.
完蛋了
Shit balls.
- 真有创意 史帝夫 - 不要叫我史帝夫
- Very original, Steven. - Don't call me Steven.
我可以穿我那件豹纹泳衣
I can wear that little leopard bikini of mine.
那件好 你穿起来很漂亮
I love that one. It's so cute on you.
帮我拉一下
Help me zip, please.
- 看过我那双粉红色鞋子吗? - 配你的粉红色泳衣吗?
- Did I show you my cute pink shoes? - Does it match your pink bikini?
她们在脱衣服
They're getting naked.
- 好看 - 谢谢
- Cute. - Thank you.
过瘾 她在脱裤子
Shit. She's de- pantsing.
天哪
Oh, man.
她们听不到我们说话 不会干扰吧?
Wait. They can't hear us inside? We won't cross over their radio?
不会 我们用的是CB频率
No, man. These work on a CB frequency.
有够正点
This girl is so hot.
女同志现在只剩胸罩和内裤
Two possible lesbians in their bras and panties.
女同志?
Lesbians?
你刚才说女同志吗?
Did you say lesbians?
正点的女同志
Hot lesbians!
- 别碰我 - 我没有啊
- Don't touch me. - I'm not.
你要是敢再拿你的弟弟戳我 你就死定了
That better not have been what I thought it was.
穿不下 你看我就知道了
This is not gonna fit. Look at you and look at me.
- 太大了 - 我拿蓝色那件给你
- Too big. - I'll get you the blue stringy number.
强尼牛仔不见了
Johnny West is missing.
也许在你床底下
Maybe you kicked it under the bed.
我找找看
Okay, let me look.
不对 你是不是拿到楼下去了
Wait. Didn't you have it when we were downstairs?
搞不好
Maybe.
你们还不快闪
Guys, get the hell out of there right now.
快点 快点
Come on!
- 没人 - 快走
- It's clear! - Go, go, go!
她们回来了
They're coming back.
还好找到 这是我最喜欢的玩具
I'm just so glad I found him. He's my favorite collectible.
我知道
I know.
我想起来了 ！我们根本不用担心
Guys, we got nothin' to worry about.
那根棒棒是我从 另一间房间里拿来的
I just remembered, I got that dildo from the other bedroom.
怎么会有一根情趣棒
Holy shit! There's a dildo in my drawer.
你要用的话为什么不跟我借
Oh, my God! You could have asked me if you wanted to borrow it.
别吵
Stop it.
- 什么声音? - 我不知道 打电话报警
- What the hell was that? - I don't know. Call 911.
- 不要打911 - 不要报警
- No 911 . - Don't call the police.
- 是那群油漆工 - 我还是要报警
- My God, it's the painting kids. - I'm still calling the cops.
不要 不要 听我说
Okay, no, no, no. This isn't right.
- 是史勒偷溜进来 - 烂人
- Look. Stifler did break in here. - You dick!
我们只是要叫他出去
But we just followed him in to get him out.
我只是想证明你们是同性恋
I just wanted proof that you chicks are really lesbians.
要不要整他们?
You wanna mess with 'em?
对 好主意
Yeah, it'll be fun.
- 来吧 - 来吧
- Let's do it. - Let's do it.
你们喜欢?
You guys like that?
欧兹 等我确认
Ozzy, stand by for confirmation.
千万不能马虎
That's a big 10-4 on the confirmation.
你朋友好像也想加入的样子
Sounds like your little friends outside wanna play too.
这个你用不到
You won't be needing this.
有谁要我摸安柏?
Who wants me to touch Amber?
我 我要
I do, I do.
- 那又是谁? - 你是谁?
- Who the hell is that? - Who's this?
我是约翰史密斯
This is John Smith.
(音量)
我现在把收音机关掉
I'm turning off my radio now.
那我应该摸哪呢?
Okay. Where should I touch Amber?
屁股 摸她屁股
Ass, baby. Feel that ass!
好舒服
That's nice.
想到了 你先摸他的屁股
I know. You feel his ass first.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
- 好主意 我喜欢 - 不错吧
- Yeah, I like that. That's good. - It's good.
我还没油漆完 我该...
Yeah, so I got some painting I should... It's...
吉姆 等一下 我可以
Jim, hold on. I can handle it.
- 什么? - 我对自己有信心
- What? - I'm comfortable with my sexuality.
我愿意牺牲
And I would love to see that show.
好耶
Bravo!
用手指头 碰一下
One finger on the cheek.
我们要你
We want...
用手掌抓
palm grasping.
太过份了 不行
That's too much. No, no, no.
你不摸 我们也不摸
You don't touch, we don't touch.
- 用力捏 包你喜欢 - 快点啊
- Squeeze his ass, son. You'll like it. - Come on, boys.
- 老天爷 - 妈的
- Jesus Christ. - Oh, shit.
只是肉 没什么了不起
I'm touching his ass. I'm touching his ass.
红队 报告位置
Red Leader, what's your position?
只是肉 没什么了不起
I'm touching his ass. I'm touching his ass.
妈
Mommy!
你去好了
We can go.
那没什么
That really wasn't bad.
- 我要回家 - 太可惜了
- I wanna go home. - That's too bad.
没关系 我留下来
Never mind. I'm staying.
丹妮正在摸我的胸部
Danielle is feeling my breasts.
该我
No way, dude!
她的胸部好圆
Her breasts are so luscious.
你买的什么圣诞礼物
What a wonderful Christmas gift you bought the boys.
我的乳头好硬哦
My nipples are so hard.
我有办法修好
I think I can fix these.
老天爷
SweetJesus.
换你了
Your turn.
好耶
Oh, yeah!
跟他
Him.
接吻
Kiss.
别想
Dude, no.
- 什么? - 想看的话
- Wait. What? - Oh, yeah. You want more?
就要听话 快去
We want more. Go get him, tiger.
- 你会喜欢的 - 为了我们
- You're gonna love it. - Do it for us.
好吧
Okay, dude.
一、二
One, two...
三
three.
- 那不算 - 怎么不算
- That doesn't even count. - That totally counted.
- 像在亲你妈一样 - 给我闭嘴
- That's how you kiss your mother. - Don't you say anything!
逼真一点
Make it real.
做得到
You do that...
什么要求我们都答应
we'll do anything you want.
任何要求?
Anything?
任何要求
Anything.
最好不要骗我
You better like it.
- 我保证 - 保证
- Promise. - I promise.
绝对不骗你
I wouldn't lie.
来吧
Come on.
就像这样
That is what I'm talking about.
凯文 让你看
Kev, you can look.
很好
That's it.
舌头呢?
Where's your tongue?
乖孩子
Good boys.
- 非常好 - 你到底会不会接吻
- Very good. - Dude, you're a fucking lousy kisser.
我是随便亲的
What? I wasn't trying!
不公平
That's not fair!
我只是随便亲亲 真的
I wasn't trying there. I'm really...
- 我只是... - 没意见
- I'm not... - No judgment.
- 没意见 - 你真的在亲?
- Nope. - Wait a second. You were trying?
- 当然没有 - 你真的在亲
- Fuck no! - You were trying!
- 天哪 恶心死了 - 我亲了他
- Oh, my... That's disg... - I kissed Jim!
别吵 别吵
Silence. Silence. Silence!
- 小姐们 - 干嘛?
- Ladies. - Yes?
换你们了
As you were.
- 换我们了 - 来吧
- Here we go. - Let's do it.
那两个小姐听起来 跟上次搭我们便车的人妖好像
Them girls sound like the two transvestites we picked up in Biloxi.
- 老公 吃饭了 - 我不饿
- Honey, come on. Food's ready. - I'm not hungry!
真是太扯了 好吧 要玩就玩到底
I can't believe this. Okay,just do it.
- 天哪 - 值得牺牲
- Oh, God. - It was worth it.
你们好
Hello.
千万别停
Keep goin'.
好了 我们到此为止 好啊
Okay, I think that's enough now. That's good.
- 我还要 - 是啊 我们要再接再励
- I want more. - Hell, yeah. I want more too, baby.
进入高潮前 我们先...
We're gonna get more physical as soon as we get some...
- 打手枪 - 没问题
- Hand jobs. - Okay!
打手枪
Hand jobs.
你帮他打 我们喜欢看
You do him. We love to watch.
再说一遍
I'm sorry?
- 你们先做 - 我们再做
- You go. - We go.
别害羞嘛
Don't be a wimp.
没关系 没关系
Okay. It's okay.
我知道该怎么做
I know what I have to do.
让游戏继续下去
I need to keep this party goin'.
我愿意为大家牺牲
I'm takin' one for the team.
我的妈
Mother of God!
你们这些胆小鬼
Come on, you pussies! We had 'em!
- 你别想我摸 - 快把它收起来
- I am not touching that. - Put that thing away, Stifler.
你们怎么这么不合群?
Why can't you guys be team players, huh?
最吃亏的是我
I was the one doin' all the sacrificin'.
各位亲爱的忠实听众们 欢迎回到节目现场
And now for our devoted listeners, back to the show.
安柏 把那根情趣棒借我用用
Let me try that dildo.
等一下
Now wait just a minute.
史勒要帮你们打手枪?
Stifler wanted to give you two hand jobs?
错 是我们帮他
No. Stifler wanted one from us.
真的假的?
What? Bullshit.
骗你干嘛 吓死人了
He did. And it was horrible.
非常恐怖
Very horrible.
要玩牌吗?
You guys, you wanna play some ''asshole''?
看球赛好了
Just watching the game, Kev.
只是想大家一起做点事
I just wanna do something together.
我们才刚一起做完一件事
We just did something together.
- 一件大事 - 吼吼吼
- Very together. - Ho, ho, ho.
圣诞老人来了
Stifler Claus is here.
为了避免我们误入歧途
Now,just so there's no confusion...
咸湿圣诞老人送了色情录影带来
Santa Porn has just brought us some heterosexual entertainment.
你的
Here you go.
这是你的
All right. Here.
还有我友情赞助的润滑油
And the Stifmeister's provided us some complimentary lubricant.
试试看 别客气
Whack away,Jim. Whack away.
这东西真的有用吗?
Does this stuff really make a difference?
当然
Oh, yeah!
真的?
Really?
史勒爱的宫殿
Stifmeister's palace of love...
异性爱
straight love.
嗨 我很好
Oh, hey. Yeah, I'm fine.
- 你呢? - 他妈妈打来的
- How about you? - That's Stifler's mom.
安静
Silence.
没想到你整个暑假都待在密西根
I didn't really think you were gonna be in Michigan this summer.
当然欢迎你来
Yeah, you're more than welcome to be here.
过几个礼拜 我们要开大型派对
Okay, stop by in a couple of weeks. We're having a big party.
好 再见
Okay, bye.
史勒 那是...
Stifler, was that...
她要过来
She's coming.
他妈妈要过来
Stifler's mom is coming here.
要加倍练习
Efforts must be doubled.
''Efforts must be doubled.''
当然
Absolutely.
(高橡树)
你看到我的竖笛吗?
Jenny, where'd you put my clarinet?
- 我帮你塞进盒子了 - 谢谢
- I think I shoved it in your box. - Thanks.
非礼勿视 非礼勿视
Bad man. I'm a bad, bad man.
你来干嘛?
Jim, what are you doing here?
这个 我以为你说...
I... Well, I thought you had said...
不能站在这边
You can't just stand out here.
我需要你帮忙
Look, I need your help.
娜迪雅回来了
Nadia's coming back...
可是我...
and I don't...
我不希望跟她在一起
I don't wanna be this awkward...
还是手足无措、语无伦次
bumbling, nervous guy with her.
我不想当个笨蛋
I don't wanna seem like a dork.
我知道你的意思
Well, I know that feeling.
在乐队待久了
Spend your life playing in the band...
别人都会觉得你很土
it doesn't exactly give you the ultra- cool hipster image.
- 我觉得你很酷 - 真的?
- I think you're pretty cool. - Seriously?
为什么后来不理我?
Michelle, why did you ditch me after prom?
我没有不理你 只是...
I didn't ditch you. I just...
我们的约会结束了
Our date was over.
难道你要面对...
I mean, did you want some...
第二天尴尬的场面吗?
funky, weird, next- morning good- bye?
我不希望你假装喜欢我
It's not like I wanted you to pretend you were in love with me or something.
干嘛要假装?
Why would I pretend that?
男生都会
Guys do that.
我跟其他男生不一样
Yeah, well, I'm not like other guys.
我知道
I know.
好 我帮你
Okay, I'm gonna help you.
真的?
Really?
因为我觉得上次不该那样说你
Yeah, I feel bad for saying that you sucked...
虽然你是真的有点逊
even though you kind of did.
我是说...
I'm just...
直接开始吧
Let's just get started.
- 假装我是个辣妹 - 好
- Now, I'm a hot girl. - Right.
- 你要怎么做? - 摸你的咪咪
- Okay, what do you wanna do? - I wanna feel your boobs.
笨蛋 不对
No, you dingbat.
哪有人这样的
You don't just go groping away.
应该先来一段前戏
You gotta preheat the oven before you stick in the turkey.
亲我 这边
Kiss me, here.
对 很好
Good. Okay, now...
亲...锁骨
the collarbone... kiss.
很好
Good,Jim.
我开始兴奋了
You're making me wet.
你说真的?
Holy shit. Really?
假的 我是在帮你练习
No, I was just saying that so you could practice.
知道了
Of course.
方向有影响吗? 应该是顺时钟?还是逆时钟
Does direction matter, like clockwise, counterclockwise?
吉姆 这就是我要说的
Okay,Jim, this is what I'm talking about.
你最大的问题是...你太紧张了
Your main problem is you're so uptight.
我有因为生理需求紧张吗?没有
Do I seem uptight about my sexual stuff? No.
我只能告诉你
The biggest pointer I could give you is...
不管什么情况 都要有自信
you have to feel comfortable in any situation.
站起来
Stand up.
- 假装你搞砸了 - 前戏呢?
- Now, this is a fucked-up situation. - What happened to preheating?
- 先跳过那一段 - 好
- We're skipping a few chapters. - Oh, okay.
八成我表现得不错
This is good. This is good. Obviously.
- 荒岛历险记 - 什么?
- Gilligan's Island, Mr. Howell. - What?
控制一下自己 想些其他的事
You've got to control yourself and think of something nonsexual.
我还没碰你 你就这么兴奋了
I haven't even touched you yet, and you're turning into the Sears Tower.
对不起 想其他的事
I'm sorry. Yeah, nonsexual.
说得对
Right, right. Okay.
- 椅子 - 很好
- Chairs. - Good.
长毛象
Mastodons.
洗厕所
Cleaning my bathroom.
- 蜣螂 - 很好
- Dung beetles. - Good.
- 是的 - 千万别吓到
- Yeah. - Okay. Now, don't freak out.
我要帮你打破心理障碍
I'm gonna do something to push your threshold.
好冰 你在干嘛
Oh, that's cold! What are you doing?
把喇叭塞进你屁股 好玩吧
I just shoved a trumpet in your ass. Aren't instruments fun?
我现在是心里受到伤害
Okay, I think you've just crossed my threshold.
两个礼拜后打电话到我家 我们再继续
Call me in two weeks. I'll be home then. We can finish lessons.
知道了
Okay.
记住 别老伸舌头
Pointer... less tongue.
- 这是什么?访客登记簿 - 你看这栏
- What is it? A guest book? - Yeah, and look at this entry.
最棒的是汤姆麦尔办的派对
''Best thing was the blowout at Tom Meyers' place.
- 这是他 - 难忘的一夜
- There he is. - A night not soon to be forgotten.
93年8月 那是你哥
August '93.'' It's your brother, man. Look.
对 他租的小屋就在下面
Yeah, his cottage was right down on the beach.
我们的派对应该像那样
Guys, this is what our party's gotta be.
- 让我们难以忘怀 - 一点都没错
- Something we'll always remember. - Yes, definitely.
完全正确
Absolutely.
- 轮你钓鱼 - 我们玩的是大老二
- You go fish. - Finch, we're playing gin.
大老二
Gin.
(来自费城的问候)
(亲爱的吉姆: 我想见你 爱你的娜迪雅)
搞屁啊?
What the fuck?
(来自芝加哥的问候)
亲爱的吉姆
''DearJim.
芝加哥很美 有你在会更好
Chicago is beautiful, but it would be better if you were here.
等不及想见你 爱你的娜迪雅
I'm counting the days. Love, Nadia.''
我也希望你在这里
Well, I wish you were here, Nadia.
(湿乐园)
- 饥渴吗? - 我好饥渴
- Have you been dirty? - Oh,yes, baby. I've been dirty.
要不要我帮你?
Do you want me to clean you?
使用数滴 达到所需的润滑效果
''Apply a few drops to achieve desired lubrication.''
好吧
All right.
你兴奋是因为我的关系吗?
Is that a loofah, or are you just glad to see me?
管他的
What the hell.
天哪
Shit.
God!
以前怎么没想到
I been missin' out.
天哪
Oh, shit!
(疯狂胶: 粘力超强)
完蛋了
Shit!
- 没事吧? - 我没事
- Everybody okay? - I'm fine.
没事 一切正常
I'm fine. Everything's fine.
别吵 否则小心我过来揍你
Shut the fuck up or I'll break down this door and pummel your ass!
别过来 我没事 只是摔了一跤
No, don't come in here. I'm fine. I just fell out of the bed.
- 你确定? - 好吧 晚安
- You sure? - Okay, good night, then.
- 晚安 - 明天见
- 'Night. - We'll see you in the morning.
糟了 糟糕了
Shit! Oh, shit!
- 有毒物品防治中心 - 喂?
- Poison control. - Hello?
是这样的
Yeah, I kind of...
我自己粘住...
Super Glued myself...
自己了
to myself.
不要 不要派救护车
Don't send an ambulance.
你知道...屋子里有什么可以用的
Look, is there anything, you know, around the house?
油漆稀释剂
Paint thinner.
(油漆稀释剂)
天啊
Shit.
站住 不准动
Don't move! Stay where you are!
把手举起来
Hands where we can see 'em!
两只手 另外一只手也举起来
Both hands! Get the other hand up, goddamn it!
没办法 我被粘住了
I can't! I can't! I'm glued!
我被粘住了 抱歉
I'm glued! Sorry.
双手放松
Relax your hands.
交给我吧
I'll take it from here, okay?
阿姆 别担心 你会没事的
Don't worry,Jimbo. You're gonna be fine, buddy.
别难过 人非圣贤
Jim, this happens to the best of us.
左脚先 慢慢来 很好
Left foot first. Easy does it. Good.
- 小心头 - 好 坐下来
- Watch your head. - All right. Take a seat.
对不起 请问你是家属吗
Excuse me, sir. Are you a family member?
当然不是 我只是想看热闹
Fuck, no! This is just too good to miss!
那你就必须在这边等
Okay, sir, you're just gonna have to wait here. All right?
这个暑假果然不同凡响
This summer's turned out to be great.
使用胶水这种东西... 本来就有一定的危险性
Mucilage is, uh, dangerous territory...
我认为任何胶水类的产品
and I would think any adhesive product...
都应该要加印警告标示在上面
would have a warning right on the tube.
我以为那是润滑剂
I thought it was a lubricant.
我本来是想要用...
I was trying to use...
润滑剂
lubricant.
先生 这种淫秽的东西 请你不要拿出来跟大家分享
Son, couldn't you have left that disgusting thing at home?
你说什么?
Excuse me?
你这样会侮辱到很多女性同胞
Well, that kind of material is offensive to me.
是喔 真不好意思
Oh, well, we're sorry.
你以为我儿子喜欢 手粘着A片到处乱跑吗?
But, you see, my son couldn't leave it at home...
难道你看不出 他是来看急诊的?
because he's having a bit of a medical emergency.
谢谢 爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
我儿子对视听娱乐的品味 你也许并不苟同
Your opinion of his taste in video rentals, I'm afraid...
但我们又没问你
is not a priority, lady.
好了啦 爸爸
Okay, Dad.
我们对欧巴桑的意见没兴趣
It's at the bottom of the totem pole.
谢谢你 爸爸
Thank you. Okay?
我的宝贝儿子...
My son...
之所以坐在这里
is sitting here right now...
是因为他的手 被粘在他的老二上了
with his hand glued to his penis!
你能够体会我们的痛苦吗? 不能是吧
But that doesn't mean anything to you, does it?
那是因为你没有老二
Because you don't have a penis!
- 也许你是阴阳人 - 爸！
- Or maybe you do! - Dad!
对不起 对不起
Sorry. I'm sorry.
你知道我最讨厌的就是
You know, it just bugs me when people speak...
说话不用大脑的人
before they think.
真是狗嘴吐不出象牙来
You know, if they speak.
- 你还好吧?儿子 - 我好多了
- How you doin', son? - I've been better.
情况不算太糟嘛
Boy, that doesn't look too bad,Jim.
谢谢你 医生
Good job, Doctor.
大概八到九天就会消肿
The swelling should subside in about eight or nine days.
八...八到九天
Eight or nine...
再一个礼拜就是沙滩派对 娜迪雅也要来了
Beach party's in a week. Nadia's coming.
医生 我儿子七天后有个派对
Doctor, my son has a party in seven days...
还有一位小姐要来看他
and there's a young lady coming...
他一直等着...
that he's been waiting to...
等着跟她更进一步
he's been waiting to get with.
我劝你儿子连想都别想
I'd tell your son to keep his pants on during that party.
当然 我一定会劝他
Oh, yes. Believe me, I will be doing that. It goes without saying.
只是万一他...
But if his pants...
忍不住想了的话
decide to come off during the party...
他能够真正的随心...
could he have full use of his...
所欲吗?
penis?
好吧
Okay.
这应该可以让他少等几天
This should shave a couple of days off.
太好了
Oh, good.
谢谢你 医生
Thank you, Doctor.
吉姆
Jim...
好消息哦
that's good news.
今天还不算太糟 穿上吧
This has been a good- news day, son. Here. Put this on.
外面有点冷
Little chilly out there.
我们到了
Well, here we are.
儿子
You know,Jim...
今晚的事 我觉得不用告诉你妈
I think we should keep your mother in the dark about the incident tonight.
她知道了只会更紧张
I think the whole glue thing might get her a little queasy.
我都不知道自己在想什么
I don't know how I get myself into these things.
谢谢你能体谅我
But thanks for understanding.
你向来都很酷
You've been really cool.
我是说 在很多事情上
I mean, between this and...
你知道的
you know...
不管别人叫你阿姆 还是阿吉
You know, you may be Jimbo orJumbo...
不管你朋友怎么叫你
orJimbodinny to these guys in here, but...
对你妈跟我来说
I want you to know there are two people...
你永远都是吉姆拉文
who still remember where James Emanuel Levenstein came from.
儿子 我们以你为荣
We're awful proud of you, son.
爸 谢谢你
Thanks, Dad.
别忘了你的消肿药膏
Don't forget your penis cream.
感觉到了
That was it.
就是刚才 完全的入定
Right there. That was a pure tantric moment.
植物、水...都有催情的效果
The ficus, the water... it was all erotic.
差点就达到灵肉合一的境界
One more stimulant, I would have had full release.
你给我离那盆植物远一点
Finch, stay the fuck away from that ficus.
它可没得罪你
That's a jizz- free ficus.
早啊 阿姆 好一点没
There he is. Morning,Jimbo. How's the twig and giggleberries, man?
现在五颜六色 一块青、一块紫
Oh, very colorful. My dick looks like a paint- by- numbers.
你连自己的弟弟都不会用
You're the only guy I know whose dick needs an instruction manual.
你已经到了?没关系
What, you're here now? No, that's cool.
只要你不介意跟他们一起
You know, if you want to hang out with these guys.
好 我出来接你
Okay, then. I'll meet you out front.
- 史勒 那是... - 闭嘴 变态
- Hey, Stifler, was that... - Eat shit, Shitbreak.
她来了
She's here.
我的情人来了
My lady has arrived.
- 我去准备一下 - 去吧
- I gotta prepare. - Here we go.
- 史勒他妈也来了? - 这下精彩了
- Great. Stifler's mom is here? - This could be a disaster.
没想到他妈竟然骑机车
Not unless Stifler's mom drives a moped.
机车?
Moped?
猪头们 你们好
Fuckers, fuckers, fuckers. How you doin', boys?
- 他是史勒的弟弟 - 你来干嘛
- That's Stifler's little brother. - What are you doing here?
妹妹 我是来泡妞的
Pussy, man. I'm here for the pussy.
排队吧
Take a number.
吵什么? 不知道今天对我很重要吗?
Gentlemen, why all the noise? Everybody knows this is my special day.
- 他是谁? - 那是洋装吗?
- What is that? - Is that a fuckin' dress?
- 你穿的是洋装吗? - 变态 这是我弟
- Are you wearing a dress? - Shitbreak, meet my little brother.
小弟 他是变态
Little brother, meet Shitbreak.
- 他是你弟? - 对
- That's your brother? - Yes.
我的情人没来
My lady's not coming.
我辛辛苦苦
So my entire...
储存的子弹都白费了
stockpile is wasted...
我简直像个白痴
and I look ridiculous!
失陪一下
Excuse me.
- 情况不太对 - 不对
- That didn't look too good. - No.
- 去看你的房间 - 那些妹妹死哪去了?
- Let's go find your room. - So, where are the fuckin' females?
终于等到你一个人在家了
I can't believe Ifinally got you alone.
等了有六个礼拜吧?
That only took, what, six weeks?
你也是一个人吗?
So, are you alone too?
- 没错 - 很好
- Yep. - Good.
只有我一个人
I'm all alone.
你猜我在想什么?
Guess what I had in mind?
马可 麻烦你把球拿开
Hey, Marco, can you get your balls off me?
- 谢谢 - 发生了什么事?
- Thanks. - What the hell's going on over there?
没什么 我室友回来了
Nothing. It's just my flatmates.
看样子又泡汤了
I guess this is kind of a lost cause, huh?
- 我看也是 - 这个周末见
- Yeah, I guess so. - See ya this weekend?
- 我等不及了 - 我也是
- I can't wait. - I can't wait either.
再见
Bye- bye.
- 想不到吧 - 天啊 娜迪雅
- Surprise! - Holy... Nadia!
你来了 你来干嘛的
You're here? You're here. What are you doing here?
我看风景看烦了
Jim, I got so tired of sightseeing.
但是你...你来早了
But you're... you're early.
好吧 很高兴认识你
Okay. Nice to know you.
- 我走了 - 不要
- I will leave. - No!
不要...不要走
No. Don't... Don't leave.
不要走 别走
Don't leave. No leaving.
只是我...还没有准备好
It's just, I'm not gonna be ready...
我是指派对 派对星期六才举行
I mean, the party won't be ready until Saturday.
那我可以留下来等啊
I can stay here until then?
对
Yeah.
马上回来 等我一下
I'm gonna be right back. Is that okay?
- 好 - 娜迪亚...
- Okay. - Nadia.
竟然在我房间里 完了
Who's in my room. Now. Holy shit.
好 我有办法了
All right, I've got a plan.
干脆我跟你回去
Okay. How about I come back with you...
然后你说...
and you say...
这是我的女朋友 蜜雪儿
''Hello, this is Michelle, my girlfriend.''
这样 娜迪雅就不会逼你上床了
And obviously, Nadia won't expect you to hop in the sack.
然后到派对那天 我们再分手
And then we break up the day of the party.
你也已经完全康复了
And you're all healed and back on the market.
- 你好邪恶哦 - 才怪
- You're evil. - No way!
我像邱比特
I'm like Cupid.
而且我知道怎样让女生吃醋
And I know how to make a girl jealous.
一定会很好玩
This is gonna be fun.
抱歉 我应该早点告诉你
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner...
我们是最近才开始交往的
but we just started seeing each other a few weeks ago.
我真的...非常希望你留下来
But I'd really love it if you stayed here.
留下来参加派对
I think you should stay and have fun at the party.
谢谢你 我当然会留下来
Good for you,Jim. Of course I will stay.
太好了...那是我的奶头
That's great... That's my nipples!
她就是喜欢捏我
She just loves my nipples.
- 天哪 不 - 还没好吗?
- Oh, my God. - You still broken?
不是 我好了
I'm fine.
终于不用再包尿布了
I might have to actually go through with this.
娜迪雅有什么特别?
What's the big deal with Nadia, anyway?
我知道 她比其他的女生
I mean, okay, so she's 50,000 times hotter...
要辣好几千倍
than most girls, but...
那也只是身材啊
come on, it's just sex.
你看过我们在网络上
You saw the thing on the Internet.
我那时候看起来...
Did it look like I might have had...
像对娜迪雅有意思吗?
a slight interest in Nadia then?
现在还是一样
Add another year to that.
好吧
Okay.
带她来听音乐会啊?会很棒的
Hey, why don't you bring Nadia to the concert first? It'll be a cool date.
到时候再说吧
We'll see how things go.
蜜雪儿 谢谢你的帮忙
Michelle, you have been great.
谢谢
Thank you.
别客气
Anytime.
走吧
Come on.
准备要分手了吗?
You ready to break up?
你这个大笨蛋
You big, stupid dummy!
效果不错哦
Theater is so cool!
不管你是不是最好的床伴
I don't care if you are the best lay I've ever had in my life.
- 我都讨厌你 - 别这样
- I hate your guts anyway. - Don't say that.
就算连续给我十次高潮都没用
And I don't care if you did give me ten orgasms in a row...
因为你一身臭味
because you smell really bad.
是我一身臭味
I smell really bad!
因为我们做太多爱做的事
Because we've been having so much sex, and...
害我没洗澡 我要洗澡
and I haven't showered, and I wanna shower!
别以为自己是超级猛男
So, don't you go being all super sexy guy anymore...
你的男子气概
because I am now impervious...
你的性感 对我完全没用
to your unrelenting machismo and sexual ardor.
连肛交也没用 再见
And that includes fucking me in the ass! So there!
我们有过愉快的时光
We had something special.
- 怎么样啊? - 怎么样?老兄
- What's up? - What's up, dog?
- 维琪 - 嗨
- Vicki. - Hey.
你来啦 要喝点什么...
I'm so glad you came. You want something to drink or...
有事吗?
Can I help you?
- 凯文 - 干嘛?
- Kevin. - What?
他是我的男伴
That's my date.
你全都留着
You... You saved them all.
好细心哦
How sweet.
你不觉得我呆?
You don't think I'm a dork?
不管怎样 我都喜欢你
Whatever you are,Jim, it is what I like.
凯文走了 表情怪怪的
Kevin left. Didn't look good.
凯文走了?
Kevin left?
在海边晃
Just wandered down the beach.
你还好吧?
You okay, Kev?
想不想聊聊?
Wanna tell us what's up?
想不想摸芬奇的屁股?
Wanna feel Finch's ass?
不想 我去跟维琪打招呼
No, I... I went to say hi to Vicky...
她带了男伴来
and she was there with a date.
你认识了三个女生 没问题的
You hooked up with three girls this year. You're doing fine.
欧兹 三倍定律
Rule of three, Oz.
我大概还是希望像以前那样
I guess I was living in the past... wanting to party with you guys...
跟你们混 跟维琪在一起
and be with Vicky, just like high school.
记不记得毕业舞会那天?
You remember that day after prom?
我们举杯庆祝人生的新阶段
You know, we made a toast to the next step.
但是我从来都不愿意去面对
I guess I never took it.
我哥说等到放完假 我就明白了
My brother said that by the end of the summer I'd see the big picture.
现在我明白了
And I see it.
人不可能活在过去
No matter what, times change and things are different.
问题是 我不想长大
The problem is, I don't want them to be.
其实 我也一直活在过去
You know, Kevin, I haven't moved on either.
虽然知道不可能有结果
I've been obsessed with the one woman I can't have a real future with...
还是一直迷恋那个女人
other than a very kinky, extremely warped one.
我必须寻找新的偶像
I got to find a new goddess.
这需要耐心 但是我的忍功一流
It's gonna take patience, but I've been celibate all summer.
- 你不是早就习惯了? - 什么意思?
- You kinda get used to it, though, huh? - Are you insane?
看吧 凯文 改变不见得不好
Look, Kev, different does not necessarily mean worse.
我反而觉得越来越好
As a matter of fact, I think things are just getting better.
需不需要拖你回去 证明给你看
Or am I gonna have to drag your ass back to that party and prove it to you?
我自己会走
I'll walk.
喔
Wow.
知道吗?你的眼睛好美
You know, you have beautiful eyes.
- 谢谢你 - 好漂亮的上衣
- Oh, you're sweet. - That's a really nice top.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Oh. Thanks. - You're welcome.
- 有性趣吗? - 别开玩笑了
- Wanna fuck? - Are you serious?
我可是性爱大师哦
Come on, baby. Give it to the Stifmeister.
- 你给我... - 你的损失
- I think you better... - Your loss.
知道吗?你的眼睛好美
Wow. You know, you have beautiful eyes.
给我过来 你简直是丢脸
Come here, dude. Come on. You're making an ass out of yourself.
我的脸都被你丢光了 你不是性爱大师
You're ruining my mojo. And you're not the Stifmeister, okay?
那需要好几年的修练
It takes years to develop true Stifmeister style.
我只不过是想看辣妹
Come on, man! I just wanna see some boobs.
- 嗨 蛋塔 - 去死 侏儒
- Hey, Pop Tart. - Dream on, midget.
别理他 拿着 你负责把风
Excuse him. Come here. Take this. You're on cop watch.
去车道上看着 条子来通知我
Go out in the driveway. See any cops, call me, okay?
好的
All right.
各位 这边好像有派对
Gentlemen, this appears to be a party.
失陪了 我去找娜迪雅
Guys, if you'll excuse me, I'm gonna go look for Nadia.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你今年过得如何?
So what was this year like for you?
会怀念高中吗?
Did you miss high school?
还好
Well, no.
我常常旅行 习惯了要向前看
When you travel as much as I do, you get used to moving on.
但是我有许多美好的回忆
But I have great memories.
- 我们可以过去吗? - 灯塔?
- Wow, can we go in there? - The lighthouse?
可以啊 当然可以
Yes, we can.
多罗曼蒂克啊
How romantic.
吉姆 快点
Jim, come on.
天啊 好漂亮
Oh, it's beautiful!
好棒
Cool!
我说了我对高中的回忆
Jim, I have told you my memories from high school.
你的回忆是什么?
What are yours?
是你
You.
你一点都没变
You have not changed.
别紧张 吉姆
Jim, relax.
我们只是在 怎么说 谈心
We are just, how do you say, tooting our horns.
老实说 要不紧张满难的
Actually, that is quite difficult.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
有一次在乐队营...
Well, this one time at band camp...
天啊
Holy shit.
怎么了?告诉我
What? Tell me.
有一次在乐队营
Well, this one time at band camp...
我被拉去吹伸缩喇叭
I got stuck playing this trombone.
可是我什么都不会吹
And I can't play anything at all. So I totally sucked.
大家都以为我是那个皮迪
And everyone thought I was this Petey guy...
我没办法 只好乱吹一通
but I didn't know what to think, so I just kept playing and playing...
根本不知道自己在做什么
and I didn't know what I was doing.
真好玩
It was so funny!
- 我得走了 - 为什么?
- I gotta go. - What? Why?
请你不要误会
Please don't take this the wrong way...
你曾经是...
but, but you're...
是我想要的一切
you're everything that I used to want.
我也知道
And as much as I may really...
这样做我一定会后悔
really regret what I'm about to do...
可是我喜欢的是别人
there's somebody else I want to be with.
你喜欢...那个乐队怪胎
You want the band geek?
我也是个怪胎
Nadia, I am a band geek.
只是没有找到合拍的人
I just never joined the band.
去找你的怪胎吧
You go get your geek.
我有一天也会找到的
Someday I will find mine.
你好 我是凯文麦尔
Hey, Kevin Meyers.
刚才很抱歉
Hi. Sorry I was a dick before.
没关系 我是贝特
It's okay, man. My name's Brett.
- 我们想单独聊聊 - 好
- Could you give us a sec? - Sure.
你不用这么做
Look, you don't have to do this.
是我太自私
Maybe I was being selfish...
想继续当你的朋友
in wanting to be your friend.
也许根本就不可能
Maybe it's just not gonna work.
我宁愿当你的朋友也不愿失去你
I would much rather have you as a friend than not have you in my life at all.
(巨橡营距离四英里)
狂欢吧
Party on!
- 从灯塔一直到... - 帅哥
- From the lighthouse all the way... - Hey, handsome.
你怎么会在这里?
What are you doing here?
我本来要去机场接你的
I was gonna pick you up at the airport in two hours.
我提早飞回来 想要给你一个惊喜
I took an earlier flight, and I thought I'd surprise you.
- 我是很惊喜 - 没有电话反而怪怪的
- Yeah, you did. - Kinda weird without the phone, huh?
我们会习惯的
We'll get used to it.
进去聊 我拿杯饮料给你
Come on. I wanna hear all about it. Gonna grab you a drink.
我不要把什么狗屁风
Steve, this cop- watch thing is horseshit.
喂?
Hello?
烂透了
Man, this sucks.
你是谁?
Who is it out there?
我是性爱大师
It's the Stifmeister, baby.
是吗?
Is that so?
人生实在不如意
Life's a bitch, isn't it?
你不用回答 没关系
It's all right. You don't have to say anything.
我已经习惯女生不理我
I'm used to girls ignoring me.
或者嘲笑我
Or making fun of me.
雪门终结者去哪了
''Come on, Sherman. Be the Sherminator.''
像那部电影 你好聪明
Like the movie. How clever.
你不用装了
I get it, okay?
也许我是个怪胎
Maybe I am a geek.
无所谓
Whatever.
没错 你是怪胎
Yes! Yes, you are!
好耶
All right.
我是雪门终结者
I am the Sherminator.
穿越时空的性爱机械人
A sophisticated sex robot sent back through time...
要来改变一位幸运儿的一生
to change the future for one lucky lady.
我是那个幸运儿?
I am lucky lady?
没错 娜迪雅 你已经被锁定了
That's right, Nadia. You've been targeted for Shermination.
想活命就跟我来
Come with me if you want to live.
救命啊
Help!
- 蹂躏我吧 - 收到
- Fuck me, geek! - Affirmative!
见鬼了
No fuckin' way!
- 算了 - 你休想
- Forget it. - Like you have a chance.
干杯
Cheers, bud.
史帝夫 看我找到谁
Hey, Steve, look what I found.
- 别摸我的衬衫 - 你看嘛
- Dude, don't touch the shirt. - Just look.
- 嗨 - 你好
- Hi. - Hey, there.
厉害 女同志被你找到了
Brilliant. You found lesbians.
我看你是白费力气
Good luck trying to break through that force field.
- 女同志? - 我们没说过
- Lesbians? - We never said that.
- 什么? - 我们没说过
- What? - We never said that.
天哪
Oh, man.
为了上你们 我什么都肯做
I will do anything... anything... to sleep with you chicks.
我愿意抓这边所有男生的屁股
Okay? I'll grab every guy's ass in this room.
摸他们的屁股 甚至剃毛
I'll caress it, even. I'll shave some ass if they need it.
没错 我是认真的
Oh, yeah. You heard me.
真的 我愿意亲这边所有的人
It's true. I'll kiss everybody here. Dudes, chicks, everybody.
因为我对我自己有信心
Because I am comfortable with my sexuality.
真的
Oh, yeah.
至少跟我喝一杯嘛
At least have a drink with the Stifmeister.
- 好吧 - 可以接受
- All right. - That's fair.
好耶
All right.
你真的是性爱大师
You truly are a Stifmeister.
- 欢迎你回来 - 那是我的女同志
- Welcome back to the party. - Steve, those are my lesbians.
- 有一件奇怪的事 - 什么事?
- Ladies, I am down with the funky shit. - Like what?
上次开派对的时候...
One time at this party, I was drinking champagne...
谢谢 谢谢大家
Thank you. Thank you.
下一位要独奏的是 蜜雪儿哈提
Our next soloist will be Michelle Flaherty.
皮迪?
Petey?
我要被他逼疯了
This kid is killing me.
- 白痴 难听死了 - 我不是白痴
- You suck, retard. - I'm not retarded.
我是个特殊的男孩
I'm a very special boy.
这个乐队营的故事如何?
How's this for a band camp story?
各位 我们给皮迪一点鼓励
Come on, guys. Let's hear it for Petey!
这个死白痴
That untalented bastard!
- 真替他们高兴 - 对啊 太棒了
- Good for them. - It's awesome.
- 要跳舞吗? - 好啊
- Wanna dance? - Yeah.
马上就回来 来吧
We'll be back. Come on now, baby.
这个派对只能用三个字来形容
You know, there's only one word for that party.
- 酷毙了 - 疯狂透了
- Bitchin'. - Out of control.
真希望继续醉下去
Am I gonna have a hangover? 'Cause I want one.
再见
Later.
- 再见 - 拜拜
- Good-bye. - See ya.
- 翻到我们那页 - 一定要把这次的派对写下来
- Let's go to our page. - We have to write about this party.
有够疯狂 我的男伴都喝挂了
This party was crazy! Look at my date! He's passed out!
- 你在桌子下灌他 - 他酒量实在不行
- You drank him under the table. - He couldn't hack it.
- 最棒的暑假 - 没错
- Best summer ever, huh, fellas? - Absolutely.
- 可惜你没找到你的偶像 - 我玩得很开心
- Sorry things didn't work out for you. - You kiddin'? Things are great.
反正我有的是时间
I have all the time in the world.
是不是每年都这样?
So, are we gonna do this every summer?
- 当然 - 这还用问
- Hell, yeah, we are. - Of course we are, gentlemen.
我们尽量
Well, we're gonna try.
- 好漂亮的车 - 是很漂亮
- That's a sweet car. - It is sweet.
- 史勒的妈妈 - 嗨 芬奇
- Stifler's mom. - Hey, Finchy.
你怎么知道我在这里?
How did you know I was here?
我几个礼拜前打来过
I called a couple of weeks ago.
史帝夫没告诉你 我会顺道过来
Didn't Steven tell you that I was gonna drop by sometime?
他大概忘了
I guess it slipped his mind.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
珍妮
Jeanine.
很好...
Okay, well...
我一直在想 我才19岁
I've been thinking, and, you know, I'm 19 years old.
不能为了一棵树 放弃一片森林
There's a whole world out there. I can't be obsessed with one woman.
- 不可能 - 我很高兴你想通了
- Just can't be. - I'm glad you're learning, Finchy.
好 很好
Good. Good.
- 要上车吗? - 你最好把事情排开
- You want to get it on? - You better clear your schedule.
待会见
See you guys later.
你去哪?说好了要一起去吃饭的
Where are you goin', man? What about Dog Years?
给我...三天的时间
Give me, like, three days.
等一下 那该不会是...
Wait, was that... Was that who I think...
- 不是 - 一定是
- No. - Yeah.
- 我觉得是 - 我也觉得
- I think it was. - I think so too.
那家伙
Son of a...
那是谁啊?
Who the hell was that?
那是...
That was...
有人迷路了
That was... Someone was lost.
- 想去湖边 - 开错路了
- Lookin' for the lake. - Yeah, all turned around.
哪来的白痴啊 湖就在那边
What a dumb ass. The lake's right there.
芬奇怎么这么好狗运?
Incredible. How does Finch get so lucky?
羡慕什么?你有女朋友了
What are you worried about? You got a girlfriend now.
东西都拿了 出发去吃饭了
Everything in. Let's go. Pony up. Dog Years awaits.
没错 我有
Yeah, I do. Yeah, I do.
- 我有女朋友了 - 对 你有
- I have a girlfriend now. - Yeah, you do.
- 她是我女朋友 - 别兴奋了
- She's my girlfriend. - All right,Jimbo.
我们走吧！
Let's go! Let's go!
- 变态呢? - 去看电影
- Where's Shitbreak? - The movies.
- 去搭公车 - 去喝咖啡
- Took the bus. - Coffee.
等一下
Wait a second.
那辆车里到底是谁?
Who the fuck was in that car?
芬奇 我好想你
Oh, Finchy, I missed you.
哦 珍妮
Yeah. Oh,Jeanine.Jeanine.
叫我史勒的妈
Call me Stifler's mom.
哦 史勒的妈
Oh, Stifler's mom!